<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Josh Thiele</title>
    <link>http://jthiele5.github.io/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Josh Thiele</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jthiele5.github.io/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska&#39;s Big Men: Another Year of Disappointment?</title>
      <link>http://jthiele5.github.io/2021/03/24/nebraska-s-big-men-another-year-of-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jthiele5.github.io/2021/03/24/nebraska-s-big-men-another-year-of-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>This is a work in progress!Since being born in 2000, I have been raised to bleed Husker Red. It hasn’t worked out much for either football or basketball, but one weak link for at least basketball has always been our big man. Besides Isaiah Roby - who really isn’t a 5 but has played a little for OKC at center - we’ve had some pretty bad history. Too many coaches and players later, we still haven’t even won a tournament game, but I think we have some intriguing big men in 2020-2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting March Madness with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://jthiele5.github.io/2021/03/17/predicting-march-madness-with-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jthiele5.github.io/2021/03/17/predicting-march-madness-with-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundWe all look to win that lucrative $1 million dollars for that perfect bracket, but we resort to methods of picking the color mascot, flipping a coin, or now the new favorite - letting the site randomly finish your bracket for you. Based on probability, you have a 1 in over 9 quintillion - that’s 18 zeros. With a little bit of basketball knowledge and history of the tournament, you can probably bring down those odds to 1 in about 100 billion, so your dreams of that million dollars should stay dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
